

# SNAHASHIS DAS

Full-Stack(MEAN) Software Developer,

A fully skilled and certified developer with 10+ projects and **3 years** of experience in MEAN stack and Springboot technology, workingn as a backend engineer in Pietech Solution. And I believe in "Action speaks louder than words" so here few of them goes, My first portfolio link:

https://mcspraint.onrender.com

Github link: https://github.com/MC-Spraint

LinkedIn link: https://www.linkedin.com/in/mc-spraint-1484b5209/





25.07.1996



7602746149

mcspraint954@gmail.com

#### SOCIAL MEDIA



linkedin.com/in/me



craft-cv.com

### **EDUCATION**

03.2018 - 2022

Maulana Abul Kalam Azad University of Techlonogy

B. Tech in Computer Science and Engineering

#### **EXPERIENCE**

- 1. 07.2020 to 11-2020 in Ardent internship & training in MEAN stack
- 2. 16th may 2022 to present In Pietech Solution pvt. ltd, bangalore as a Backend Engineer(NestJS, Typescript)

10+ projects

Making REST APIs, GraphQl APIs, Caching, etc. For more details check my portfolio and linkedIn

## SKILLS LANGUAGES

NodeJs, Express, NestJs, building GraphQL & REST APIs

Databases: MySQL, MongoDB and PostGresQL.

All types of security aspects of an application .

Languages: Javascript, HTML, CSS,, ES6, Java, PHP, Linux

Git and Github

More skills : AWS-S3, Reddis,Angular, React, etc,

For more details checkout my linkedIn & Portfolio

English

Hindi

Bengali

#### **PERSONALITY**

Communicative

Organized

**Punctuality** 

**HOBBY** 

Creativity





